https://www.colour-ribbons.co.uk/terms-conditions/

VIEW BASKET: 0 ITEMS
You have no items in your shopping basket.
CHECKOUT
Currency:
Colour Ribbons
Search:
Search
Menu
Accessories Bakers TwineBalloonsBias BindingBowsChristmas AdhesivesChristmas Hanging DecorationsCordCurling RibbonDeco PicksEmbellishmentsFabric BowsGarlandsGift PacksGlitterLacePearl meshRafiaSacksTinselTulle NylonTwist TiesRibbon Acetate Satin RibbonGrosgrain RibbonSash RibbonsBabyHalloweenSatin RibbonBurlap RibbonHerringbone RibbonScallop RibbonCheck RibbonHessian Style RibbonSilver RibbonChristmasLurex RibbonSlit RibbonChristmas Printed RibbonMothers Day RibbonSmall SpoolsClearanceMesh RibbonSpot
RibbonConfirmation RibbonNatural ribbonStitch RibbonCurling RibbonOrganza RibbonStripe RibbonDouble SatinPlain RibbonTaffeta RibbonEvent RibbonPolypropylene RibbonTartan RibbonFlag RibbonPull Bow RibbonValentine RibbonFloral Print RibbonRed RibbonWedding RibbonGay Pride RibbonRibbon BundleWhite RibbonGingham RibbonRic RacWired RibbonGold RibbonRosette RibbonZebra RibbonCraft Acetate SatinBakers TwineBalloonsCordChristmas AdhesivesCurling RibbonDeco PicksElasticEmbellishmentsGarlandsGlitterLacePearl MeshRafiaRibbon BundlesSequin & BeadsStickersTinselTulle RibbonChristmas Christmas BagsBakers TwineBottle BagsChristmas AdhesivesChristmas Floral PicksChristmas GarlandsChristmas Hanging DecorationsChristmas RibbonChristmas StickersChristmas TinselCurling RibbonCordGift PacksGift SetsGoldGreenLurex Pearl MeshPrinted RibbonRedChristmas SacksSilverTartanWiredWreath RibbonEvents / Occasions BabyBirthdayConfirmationEasterEventGay PrideHalloweenMothers Day RibbonSpringValentines RibbonWeddingsGift Bags  &  Sacks BabyBirthday BagsBottle BagsCard Gift BagsChristmasFabric SacksOrganzaSatin BagsWeddingSales OffersFlorists BowsBurlap PrintedCurling RibbonMeshPolypropylene RibbonSatin RibbonTulle RibbonWired ProductsSashes  &  Rosettes
Home
/
Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
Terms of website use
Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use the site. By using our site (Colour Ribbons), you indicate that you accept these terms of use and that you agree to abide by them. If you do not agree to these terms of use, please refrain from using our site.Reliance On Information Posted & DisclaimerThe materials contained on our site are provided for general information purposes only and do not claim to be or constitute legal or other professional advice and shall not be relied upon as such. We do not accept any responsibility for any loss which may arise from accessing or reliance on the information on this site and to the fullest extent permitted by English law, we exclude all liability for loss or damages direct or indirect arising from use of this site.Information about uswww.colour-ribbons.co.uk & www.colour-ribbons.com is a site operated by Colour Ribbons. We are a Company registered in England and Wales, our company number is 1797348. Our VAT number is GB 399 3132 21. Accessing our siteAccess to our site is permitted on a temporary basis, and we reserve the right to withdraw or amend the service we provide on our site without notice (see below). We will not be liable if for any reason our site is unavailable at any time or for any period.Intellectual property rightsWe are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in our site, and in the material published on it. Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world.  All such rights are reserved.You may print off one copy, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from our site for your personal reference and you may draw the attention of others within your organisation to material posted on our site. You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.Our status (and that of any identified contributors) as the authors of material on our site must always be acknowledged.You must not use any part of the materials on our site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors.If you print off, copy or download any part of our site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use our site will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made.Our site changes regularlyWe aim to update our site regularly, and may change the content at any time. If the need arises, we may suspend access to our site, or close it indefinitely. Any of the material on our site may be out of date at any given time, and we are under no obligation to update such material. If we do not have items of stock available we will update you on this as soon as possible.Our liabilityThe material displayed on our site is provided without any guarantees, conditions or warranties as to its accuracy. To the extent permitted by law, we, and third parties connected to us hereby expressly exclude:- All conditions, warranties and other terms which might otherwise be implied by statute, common law or the law of equity.- Any liability for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by any user in connection with our site or in connection with the use, inability to use, or results of the use of our site, any websites linked to it and any materials posted on it, including, without limitation any liability for:- loss of income or revenue;- loss of business;- loss of profits or contracts;- loss of anticipated savings;- loss of data;- loss of goodwill;- wasted management or office time; and for any other loss or damage of any kind, however arising and whether caused by tort (including negligence), breach of contract or otherwise, even if foreseeable, provided that this condition shall not prevent claims for loss of or damage to your tangible property or any other claims for direct financial loss that are not excluded by any of the categories set out above. This does not affect our liability for death or personal injury arising from our negligence, nor our liability for fraudulent misrepresentation or misrepresentation as to a fundamental matter, nor any other liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.Information about you and your visits to our siteWe process information about you in accordance with a strict privacy policy. By using our site, you consent to such processing and you warrant that all data provided by you is accurate. Viruses, hacking and other offencesYou must not misuse our site by knowingly introducing viruses, trojans, worms, logic bombs or other material which is malicious or technologically harmful. You must not attempt to gain unauthorised access to our site, the server on which our site is stored or any server, computer or database connected to our site. You must not attack our site via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of service attack.By breaching this provision, you would commit a criminal offence under the Computer Misuse Act 1990. We will report any such breach to the relevant law enforcement authorities and we will co-operate with those authorities by disclosing your identity to them. In the event of such a breach, your right to use our site will cease immediately.We will not be liable for any loss or damage caused by a distributed denial-of-service attack, viruses or other technologically harmful material that may infect your computer equipment, computer programs, data or other proprietary material due to your use of our site or to your downloading of any material posted on it, or on any websitelinked to it.Links from our siteWhere our site contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only.  We have no control over the contents of those sites or resources, and accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them.  When accessing a site via our website we advise you check their terms of use and privacy policies to ensure compliance and determine how they may use your information. Jurisdiction and applicable lawThe English courts will have non-exclusive jurisdiction over any claim arising from, or related to, a visit to our site. These terms of use and any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with them or their subject matter or formation (including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the law of England and Wales.VariationsWe may revise these terms of use at any time by amending this page. You are expected to check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we made, as they are binding on you. Some of the provisions contained in these terms of use may also be superseded by provisions or notices published elsewhere on our site.Your concernsIf you have any concerns about material which appears on our site, please contact sales@colour-ribbons.com
PRIVACY POLICY
We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our processes and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.
PERSONAL DATA WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU
We may collect and process the following personal data about you:
Personal Data you give us
to enable you to access our Web portal and to correspond with us by phone, email or otherwise
to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about
The personal data you give us may include items such as your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. We rely on ‘contractual necessity’ as the lawful ground for the processing of your personal data in such cases.
Personal Data we collect about you
to improve our Products and to ensure that Web portal content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or device
USES MADE OF THE PERSONAL DATA
We use personal data held about you in the following ways:
Personal Data you give to us. We will use this personal data:
to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
to notify you about changes to our service;
RETENTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
We will retain your personal data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you with access to our Web portal and services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your personal data to provide you with access to our products, contact us at; uksalesoffice@colour-ribbons.com. We will only retain and use your personal data thereafter as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
The security of your personal data is important to us. We comply with accepted industry standards to protect the personal data submitted to us. We use strict procedures and advanced security features to try to prevent unauthorised access. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is however 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Portal, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. You are not permitted to share a password with anyone.
Our Web portal may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partners, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy notice of any website you visit.
YOUR RIGHTS
You have the following rights in relation to the handling of your personal data:
You have the right to request details of your personal data held about you by us
You have the right to have inaccuracies corrected for personal data held about you by us
You have the right to have personal data held about you erased / deleted
You have the right to object to direct marketing being conducted based upon personal data held about you by us
You can exercise any of your rights outlined above by contacting us at uksalesoffice@colour-ribbons.com and we will action your request within one month. Where we receive a large number of requests, or receive especially complex requests, this may be extended by a maximum of two further months. If we fail to meet these deadlines or if you feel your rights have not been adequately respected, you may complain to the Supervisory Authority and/or seek a judicial remedy.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on our web site.
CONTACT
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to uksalesoffice@colour-ribbons.com
Stay up to date with offers, products, promotions & more! (we never spam!)
© 2020 Colour Ribbons Ltd, Holmfield Ho/Holdsworth Rd, Halifax HX3 6SN
Tel: +44 (0) 1422 231100. Email: sales@colour-ribbons.co.uk
Company reg: 1797348. VAT no: GB 399 3132 21
Website by Vantage Agency
